Hey everyone! Today I'm going to show you the secret of a $200 boob job because I
received this package from Rouania and yeah today I'm going to transform into
an F cup. They mainly offer products for crossdressers and drag queens but they
have these particular set of boobs for women with a special structure on the
inside I'm going to show you in a second so I'm super curious to try them on
because I've always wanted to know how this works and how this looks and if
it's really so easy to get such a big boob. I don't know if I can show them to
you without my hands in front of them because they're not real breasts they
also don't have nipples so the meta-logic for Facebook and Instagram
should be no female nipples no problem but I'm really not sure I think they're
going to be a problem so I better play it safe also YouTube guidelines are
really confusing and you never know what you do or not allowed to do or whatever
you can do so yeah I will just try them on now these are the silicon boobs
they're available in four colors I'm wearing the lightest tone and maybe I
could have gone a color darker as you can see it is like a whole top so from
here the neck area till under the boobs and I can also turn around you can see
from the back side too it's a lot of silicone to hold everything in place and
you can use talcum to get into it what I did I used a trash bag and put it over
my head and hair to simply slide the silicone over the plastic bag and
without damaging and ruining my hair and my makeup worked pretty well so that's
definitely a way to do this but this kind of feels stupid and I still don't
know if this is okay to show this at all so I'm going to get dressed again now
this is the look I had in mind a latex bodysuit with a front zip because as you
know by now I love front zips with a front zip you can always show the girls
in the best light and now with these fake girls I'm pretty happy and I also
have to say they're pretty comfy that's also due to the fact as I said these are
the boobs especially made for female bodies they have a honeycomb structure
on the inside so they're a bit hollowed out to give room for the natural boobs
if you're a guy you have the options of silicon filling and wool filling with a
flat backside so to say but here it just cups my natural breasts really nice and
it feels really comfy it does not restrict anything or pushes anything
down which is great and they also they also bounce so it's a nice feeling and
it does not feel artificial at all so to say I'm wearing a choker to conceal the
edge of the boobs top I just call it a top now because that's basically what it
is and also a shout out to all my photo shoot girlies this is just great to give you a bigger
cup for taking pictures and photo shoots because you don't have to wear a bra and there are no
bra straps or stripes or you can't see the bra through the clothing it's just a nice smooth look
and I think f cup is pretty reasonable so changing from my c to f was okay it's not too big but they
also have bigger sizes up to whatever S cup or something like that just check
out the homepage I'll link it in the description text and I also have a
discount code so check that out too I want to try it with this zipper closed
but for that I have to get rid of the choker again now I'm trying to close it
which is pretty hard because I I cannot realize that the boobs are pretty big
and it's harder to close the zipper. So now that feels a bit more restricted due to the fact that
the latex is really tight now but it also looks nice. By the way if you hear me sniffling around
I'm basically having a cold. So that's that. So to complete the transition so to say and go all in
I have a second box here and in this box there are hip pads to...
Wait a sec...
Alright, there are hip pads to give me a bigger or wider hip part and I have to figure out how to dress them correctly but you can watch that.
So let me just put the top under the boobs.
The silicone is pretty sticky, that's what I also realized with the boobs.
I have to check in the mirror if it's supposed to be here.
Maybe.
Probably.
Like this.
So I put it a bit more like in direction of my booty.
And I think it works like that.
Of course every body type is different.
So you kind of have to figure it out for yourself.
And what works for you.
And now the difficult part is to put in the second one.
and the same position just on the other side.
And now since there is a gap between the pads and my body and the tights are just barely holding it in place,
I will put on a second pair of tights to try and lock it into place even more.
I'm scared to sit down yet, so I'll just do this standing.
Okay, I think this looks crazy.
I think it looks a bit like an hourglass figure, like big boobs and big hips.
And it's amazing how well it works with second tights on top of it.
But of course, this is not the full look.
I decided to try a catsuit with it.
Okay, I squeezed into this catsuit.
It was way harder than usually because with two pairs of tights and the hip pads and the fake boobs,
everything is just so tight.
I feel like a presswurst.
But it's a great look.
I mean, this is not how I usually look.
Obviously. Especially I think with the hips it gives Kim Kardashian vibes massively.
But it's crazy. I'm not used to that. I'm not used to looking like that. It's a bit weird.
I think personally I think the hips are too much. Like boobs are fine actually. I love them but the hips are like...
Oh. No thanks.
But the look is cool with all the PVC at the heels and of course I chose this catsuit to conceal the neck part of the fake boobs again which works like a treat.
So yeah.
Now at the end of this video I have to say the boobs are really really comfortable because I'm wearing them for quite a while now and I don't think they're too heavy.
Of course, in fact, they are over 1 kilo, so they are heavier than just a bra, but they're really comfy.
So this is a great win.
The hip pads are a nice gimmick and nice to have, but I think the boobs are definitely going to get used for photo shoots again and stuff like that.
And yeah, thanks to One Year for sending these along.
By the way, they're a sister company from Smith & Sons.
And if you hear the name Smith & Sons, you maybe remember the catsuit video with the silicone catsuit.
Check it out again, it's great. I have a discount code for both of them.
And yeah, I think I'm going to take some pictures now with this outfit.
And I'll let you decide what you like more or better.
Just the boobs, the boobs and the hips.
Do you think it's cheating? Because I don't think so.
and okay leave a comment a thumbs up subscribe to my channel check out my patreon
I will see you in the next video have a nice day bye